Now, short-form content is a lot easier.
Adam Sullivan, again, at the moment,
is just doing point and shoot.
Just takes the phone out, presses plus.
"You'll never guess what, brother.
I just saw someone in a fucking Evidence
T-shirt, brother."
And people are there like, "Oh,
amazing reel.
Fucking amazing reel."
So when people are like,
"I don't have time to post on social
media,"
you could literally squat rack. "Hi, guys.
Just in case you weren't sure,
these J-hooks here,
if you get them at chest height,
it's going to be the most comfortable for
a back squat.
Just saw someone there, the J-hook
was too high, their head's gone,
they tiptoes to
put the rack... Anyway,
if you have any questions about the squat
rack, just put
them in the comments
and I'll get back to you in a second."
Post.
You get one question.
You then reply to that question
and make a reel with the
questions in it.
"John here asks about this in the squat.
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah." Is
that reel going to get you millions of
views and
tens of thousands of clients? No,
but it's easy to produce.
You just press the button on your phone,
you point and shoot.
So that part of you,
you don't just grab your phone
and hold it sideways.
Welcome to YouTube. Today,
it needs a bit more strategy.
Long-form is less forgiving because you
can work on a long-form
video for two weeks, and
if it doesn't take off,
there's nothing you can do.
If YouTube decides not to put it in front
of people,
YouTube's like, "See
you." That two weeks, gone. You, fucked.
Doesn't care. For Instagram, you're like,
"Oh, cool, I'll just do another one
later."